https://www.gloriajeans.com/privacy-policy/

Remember me
Lost your password?
Remember me
Lost your password?
Remember me
Forgot your password?
Learn More
New to us?
Sign Up
Login
Sign Up
Toggle navigation
(0)
Your cart is empty.
MenuCoffee SubscriptionsCLOSE
(0)
Your cart is empty.
Gloria Jean’s Gourmet Coffees Corp. (“Gloria Jean’s”) is concerned about privacy on the Web. As such, we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know how Gloria Jean’s collects, uses and safeguards the information that is collected and used on gloriajeans.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy works in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions but does not modify or supersede them.
Gloria Jean’s Collection of Your Information
In the course of using the Site, Gloria Jean’s will ask you for your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, financial account information, such as credit card number and other payment information, and other registration information. Gloria Jean’s may also collect information about you such as:  if you create an account – your username, password, your city of birth, your birthday and mobile phone number.  If you buy goods at our stores or through our programs or otherwise – what you buy, where you buy, how frequently you buy and rewards you earn. Gloria Jean’s also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, FireFox, Chrome, Safari), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., ATT, Time Warner, COX Communications, Yahoo), Internet protocol (IP) address, aggregate data about the number of visits to the site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited. If you take a survey or interact with us in various other ways – demographics information and information about subjects that may interest you.
How Gloria Jean’s Uses the Information
Gloria Jean’s uses the non-personally identifiable information (“Aggregate Data”) to improve the design and content of the Site. Gloria Jean’s may use the Aggregate Data to analyze site usage as well as create products and services to fit your needs. Also, Gloria Jean’s may share this Aggregate Data with Gloria Jean’s sponsors, advertisers and other third-party vendors. Gloria Jean’s shall own such Aggregate Data and maintain copies of such as part of its records.
Except as otherwise indicated, Gloria Jean’s uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you provide: (a) to process, manage and fulfill your requests for our products and services and those of our sponsors and business affiliates and to respond to your inquiries about our offerings; (b) to communicate with you and to assist you with any questions you have about an order you have placed for products and services; (c) to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law, or as otherwise required by law; (d) to protect the security or integrity of the site; (e) to protect against a threat of safety or destruction of property; and/or (f) to protect against legal liability. In all cases, however, Gloria Jean’s agents, employees and contractors who have access to Personal Information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Gloria Jean’s will not use the Personal Information, except as set forth herein, without your permission; provided, however, Gloria Jean’s shall own all such Personal Information and maintain copies of such as part of its records.
Gloria Jean’s may also share information with companies that provide support to us (such as credit card processors, mailing houses or website hosts) and that help us market and sell our products and services (such as email vendors).  These companies may use information about you to perform their functions on our behalf.
Gloria Jean’s may use the Personal Information that it collects to offer you other products or services that Gloria Jean’s believes may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive any such information or to allow Gloria Jean’s the right to use your Personal Information as described in this paragraph, please contact Gloria Jean’s in the manner identified in the “Opt-Out” section below. The Aggregate Information and Personal Information may be transferred, distributed or sold as part of Gloria Jean’s or its assets.
How to Contact Gloria Jean’s to Opt-Out
You may choose not to receive such information and/or to allow Gloria Jean’s to use your information in the manner described above by simply notifying Gloria Jean’s directly at CustomerService@gloriajeans.com or at 1-877-320-JAVA. Upon receipt and processing of an “opt out” request, Gloria Jean’s will, within a commercially reasonable amount of time, remove your information from any future marketing communications.
Security; No Liability
Gloria Jean’s has implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under its control. Nevertheless, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on the Site, and Gloria Jean’s and its third party licensors are not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. Furthermore, the Site contains links to other sites. Gloria Jean’s is not responsible for nor can Gloria Jean’s ensure the privacy practices or content of such other sites.
Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of data sent from a Web server to a Web browser that enable a Web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by that server. Gloria Jean’s may use Cookies in order to identify you to the Site so that Gloria Jean’s can provide more customized information and services to you. In addition, the Site may contain advertisements that may contain Cookies. In general, if you choose, you can disable the use of Cookies by reviewing your browser’s preferences and options.
Modification of Privacy Policy
Gloria Jean’s may change this Privacy Policy at any time, consistent with the terms set forth in the Terms and Conditions of Use, including by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on the site. Your continued viewing of or use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.
How to Contact Gloria Jean’s for Any Reason
You may contact Gloria Jean’s with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, updating any Personal Information or anything else related to Gloria Jean’s and/or the Site at CustomerService@gloriajeans.com or at 1-877-320-JAVA.
Security
Gloria Jean’s takes reasonable steps to safeguard your purchases at gloriajeans.com. Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. We make use of appropriate commercially available software to encrypt order information.
While we take these reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information, no system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Support
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Shipping Policy
Gift Cards
Returns & Exchanges
COVID – 19 INFO – VIRUS UPDATE
Copyright © 2020 Gloria Jean's Gourmet Coffees. All rights reserved.
